One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
A Stolen Dream! Sanji vs. Absalom
W-What's going on?
That's one amazing tremor!
The ship could be caught in some weird current...
It's probably your fault.
Now then, what business do you have here?
Why did you come?
Yeah, you ripped off my shadow a while ago.
I want it back.
Also Zoro's,
and Sanji's,
and Brook's,
and the zombie old man's.
All of them!
Quite a greedy guy.
And what're you planning on doing?
I'll kick your ass!
Kick my ass?
Yeah, that's right.
If you defeat or kill me, that would just leave the zombies without their master.
The shadows won't come out.
My devil fruit ability is to rule over the shadows.
In order for your wish to be granted, this is what you do...
The current owners of the shadows must hear me give the order, "Go back to your Master."
Just by doing that, every shadow will return?
That's right! Simple, isn't it?
You can weaken me to the point of doing so, but...
With your current strength I seriously doubt you can even touch me.
Alright.
Rubber...
Pistol!
A shadow?
Let's see you win...
Against my clone,
Doppelman!
Long ago, I too was overconfident in my abilities and ambition.
Until I finally realized the need to have many more subordinates.
Who is this guy?
Hey! Move!
I don't have to move a finger.
Other people's efforts will make me Pirate King.
I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Your zombie said the same.
As expected from the shadow and body. Despite the difference in size,
He still reflects the strong will of its former master.
But it won't be for long.
Once he loses all memories of being you, he'll fully become my loyal zombie.
Regardless of how strong the will is, every zombie will end up showing absolute loyalty!
I'm taking it back now!
Rubber...
Brick Bat!
Gatling!
Damn! They're protecting him!
I can't hit him!
Don't worry, they won't suck your blood.
Kick my ass?
Don't make me laugh.
Let go of me!
An inexperienced youngster always underestimates everyone else, and gets ridiculed in the end.
You bastard! I'm through with you!
Rubber...
What? He jumped down...
Are you running away?
Stamp!
That hurt, stupid brat!
Look!
I did touch you after all, giant leek!
Skip, skip, skip...
Get your...
hands off Nami-san!
Sorry for the delay, Nami-san.
Your knight is here.
Is this...
A Goddess?
Ah, no, it's Nami-san...
Definitely Nami-san.
Without a doubt.
Ah, that surprised me...
Such beauty can be tricky.
For a second I thought I rescued a fairy by accident.
Geez...
What're you blabbering on about?
You're one of the crew members who was on the ship, aren't you?
A-An angel?!
Ah, no, no, it's a human.
No doubt about it.
That got me.
I don't blame you.
Not in the least.
Seeing Nami-san dressed in this snow white color is confusing.
Absolutely right!
What's with those two?
We're thinking alike.
Curse you, pirate!
I've no reason to get along with you!
Hey!
That could've hit Nami-san.
You should avoid attacking recklessly in a lady's presence.
Good job avoiding that.
It seems you no longer have your shadow.
Come to think of it, there was this newbie zombie who had a strange attachment to that woman.
A rebel zombie with some ego still left in him.
That was probably your zombie.
The fact that he wasn't included among the General Zombies must mean that his real body is weak.
That overconfident penguin was actually pretty weak.
It's so absurd...
for a pathetic underling to pick a fight with me, a monster and commander of the General Zombies!
A-A nymph?!
That surprised me...
I thought it was a nymph for a second.
Now, I don't wanna get rough...
Leave that woman with me and go back to your life in the shadows.
I'm busy right now...
My strongest underlings were annihilated by your stupid captain's zombie.
And before that, I couldn't even give my bride the vow kiss...
Don't you get it?
I'm terribly irritated right now.
I have no time to deal with amateurs like y-
Shut up, you Carnival-beast-face man!
Absalom-sama!
No way!
He sent that 300 kilogram body flying in an instant!
You must be the invisible man Usopp spoke of.
What's with that kick?!
Hogback improved my body with the power of the wild, and yet he blew me away...
Hands of the Dead!
What's the meaning of this?!
Did he know what I was about to do?!
Basse Côte!
Lower Rib
Longe!
Loin
You're that wild beast who licked Robin-chan on the Sunny, aren't you?!
Something grabbed me...!
You're the one who saw Nami-san completely naked in the bathroom, aren't you?
You'll be my bride.
Tendron!
Collar
Flanchet!
Stomach
Quasi!
Rump
What's with his strength?!
Is he really just an underling?!
Queue!
Tail
Cuisseau!
Thigh
Jarret!
Shin
Why is she unconscious?!
You better not have gotten violent with her!
What marriage?!
Look at my eyes! I'll kick the hell out of you and make a croquette with your remains!
Damn! I gotta avoid him!
Skating...
Usopp's Special Salt Ball...
There he is!
What?! It's salty!
Veau Shot!
Veal Shot
Impossible...
This guy doesn't even have a bounty...
You say you're irritated...?
That's nothing compared to me...
My body is exploding with rage!
It is!
And there's one more unfortunate thing...
You and I have...
A connection!
A-Absalom-sama...
You and I have a connection?
That's right, you're the man who stole my dream.
I don't remember you.
It must be some kind of misunderstanding.
Today is the first time...
I've ever met with you.
I'll blow you away!
With these Hands of the Dead!
Take them off.
I told you to take off those bazookas attached to your arms.
Don't you get it?
If Nami-san gets hurt because of your mindless attack, you won't appear very alive when I finish with you.
He knows nothing...
I told you to...
Take them off!
What?! A bazooka suddenly appeared!
That's how it is, right?
That's a very clever attack.
You make your body invisible, and anything that comes in contact with your body invisible.
That's your ability...
The Transparent Fruit's invisible man.
I know everything you're capable of!
How is that possible...?!
Who are you...?!
Has that man met Absalom-sama before?
Why does he know everything about his abilities?
When I was a kid, I saw a large picture book about the devil fruit.
At first, I wasn't interested in all those rumors about sea curses, but...
while flipping through it, I came across a single item that caught my eye.
If I happened to find that ability...
even if I was to become cursed, I'd gladly eat it!
But two of the same fruit don't exist in this world.
If by any chance, I ran into the user of that fruit, my dream would collapse!
You get it now?!
I wished to become the invisible man!
That's why, the moment you ate the
Transparent Fruit, you crushed my dream!
He's right!
I wanted my dream to come true!
If so, with that ability I'd enter the...
women's bath!
No, I'd do something honorable in the...
No, I'd definitely help the people in the...
women's bath!
He wants nothing but to peek into the women's bath!
Shut up!
But thanks to many years of simulation, I know everything you can see-
No, everything you can do with that ability!
And if we add that you put Nami-san in danger, that means I'll definitely never forgive you!
Women's ba-
No! You better be ready to die!
What're you thinking?!
What a ridiculous connection!
That's the most stupid thing I've ever heard!
You're a...!
freaking pervert!
I don't want to...!
Hear that from you!
He's right!
But they're the same!
Very well!
I'll return your connection, your rage, everything back to you!
Not only do I have a lion's jaw...!
Elephant skin...!
Three hundred kilograms of condensed bear and gorilla muscle!
Implant after implant, Dr. Hogback kept working on me until I obtained the ultimate masterpiece body!
The Transparent Fruit is nothing but an bonus.
It doesn't even compare to the terrible strength I have!
Do you understand now?
But...
You still peeked on her!
It is true!
If it had been an ordinary kick, his leg would've been destroyed...
It's just as if my body was a regular human body to him.
But I'll have the last laugh!
You lost the ability you wished for and now even the woman you intend to protect will be my bride!
You've no chance to beat me in this state!
Back then, Nami disappeared along with him and we couldn't follow him!
You want to hide Nami-san, don't you?!
Over my dead body!
It's useless!
I'll show you the power of the beast man!
So you intend to sacrifice yourself for that woman?
Protect her then!
If you can!
Beast Man's Hands!
Beast Man's Legs!
Don't let go of her!
Sorry... Nami-san...
You let her go?
So you value your life over hers after all!
Sorry...
I don't wanna stain that snow white dress...
Damn... you just hide and sneak, you invisible man...
I don't give a damn about that dream anymore...
I no longer... care about being an invisible man!
I'll peek on my own!
You still wanna peek?!
Let go of me, bastard!
Let go!
Like I would, you filthy bastard!
If you're made of many beasts...
You'll make a fine minced meat!
Shut up! Let go of me!
Extra Haché!
Haché: Mincemeat
Absalom-sama!
Women's bath...
No...
A beast's bride...
Ought to be another beast.
He's still following me!
If it wasn't for him, I'd have already beaten the other pirates!
Damn Nega-nose!
He's still following me!
If it wasn't for him, I'd have already beaten that hollow-hollow woman!
Damn bear zombie!
Wait...!
Stay away!
Wait, hollow-hollow woman!
Kumashi, hurry up and stop him!
Wait...!
Don't lay a hand on Perona-sama...!
Too close! Too close!
Perona-sama...!
What a terrifying power for a stuffed doll!
Take this!
Sure-Kill...
Blazing Ball!
It worked!
A zombie is a zombie after all!
Now, with this oil, I'll perform my
"You Won't Come Here Technique"!
What...?
Stupid bear!
You can't catch me now!
Now nothing is in my way.
Do you understand my power now?
Let's see now, I've got a hollow-hollow woman weaker than me that I must punish.
Where'd she go?
Over here, Nega-nose.
Maybe outside the window...?
Though, that's not possible...
We're in a pretty high pla-
Y-You...!
How come you can fly?!
You're supposed to manipulate ghosts only!
W-What's your real ability?!
You better not underestimate the Ghost Princess, fool.
I just thought of a way to get rid of you.
When I'm done with you, taking care of the remaining pirates won't be a problem.
Wait a minute!
I have a... bad feeling about that statement!